https://www.clearessence.com/privacy-policy

Home My Account Shopping Cart
×
Skin Care Lines
Exclusive Skin Care LineClear Essence Exclusive Skin Beautifying Milk (10 oz.)Clear Essence Exclusive Medicated Fade Creme w/ Sunscreen (4 oz.)Clear Essence Exclusive Brightening Facial Masks (5-Pack)See all...
Platinum Skin Care LineClear Essence Platinum Skin Smoothing Creme (4 oz.)Clear Essence Platinum Blemish Control Wash Formula For Acne (4 oz.)Clear Essence Platinum Specialist Skincare Body Oil (8 oz.)See all...
Anti Aging Skin Care LineClear Essence Anti-Aging Toner Astringent w/ Alpha Hydroxy Acid (8 oz.)Clear Essence Anti-Aging Complexion Soap w/ Alpha Hydroxy Acid (5 oz.)Clear Essence Anti-Aging Skin Beautifying Milk w/ Alpha Hydroxy Acid (4 oz.)See all...
Maxi-Tone Skin Care LineMaxi-Tone® Quick Tone Skin Lightening Soap With Shea Butter (5 oz.)Maxi-Tone® Quick Tone Complexion Clarifying Lotion (8 oz.)Maxi-Tone® Carrot Seed Oil Skin Whitening Soap (5 oz.)See all...
Lemon Plus Vitamin C Skin Care LineClear Essence Lemon Plus Vitamin C Perfecting Fade Serum (0.5 oz.)Clear Essence Lemon Plus Vitamin C – Vitamin A Creme (19 oz.)Clear Essence Lemon Plus Vitamin C Skin Beautifying Milk (4 oz.)See all...
Sensitive Skin Care LineClear Essence Sensitive Skin Beautifying Milk (8 oz.)Clear Essence Sensitive Moisturizing Body Oil (8 oz.)Clear Essence Sensitive Swiss Complex Collagen with Vitamin E Creme (19 oz.)See all...
My Natural Beauty Skin Tone LineClear Essence My Natural Beauty Skin Tone Moisturizing Body Lotion SPF 15 (8 oz.)Clear Essence My Natural Beauty Skin Tone Carrot Oil Soap (6.1 oz.)Clear Essence My Natural Beauty Skin Tone Olive Oil Soap (6.1 oz.)See all...
ChiMere™ Skin Care for MenChiMere™ Bump Control Cleansing Bar (5 oz.)ChiMere™ Triple Action Body Wash for Men (5.2 oz.)See all...
Baby Skin Care LineClear Essence Baby Lotion with Milk and Honey (10 oz.)Clear Essence Baby Lotion with Shea & Cocoa Butter (10 oz.)See all...
Adure™ Skin Care for WomenAdure™ Woman of Grace Natural Fairness Creme (4 oz.)Adure™ Natural Fairness Creme (4 oz.)See all..
Shop Online
For MenChiMere™ Bump Control Cleansing Bar (5 oz.)Platinum Line: Extra Strength Medicated Cleansing Bar plus Exfoliants (4.7 oz.)ChiMere™ After-Shave (Ingrown Hair Intensive Treatment) Gel 4 oz.ChiMere™ Shave Gel (Razor Bump Control + Blemish Control Wash for Acne) 4 oz.ChiMere™ Triple Action Body Wash for Men (5.2 oz.)
For BabiesClear Essence Baby Lotion with Shea & Cocoa Butter (10 oz.)Clear Essence Baby Lotion with Milk and Honey (10 oz.)Clear Essence Baby Oil with Lavender (10 oz.)Clear Essence Baby Soothing Milk Bar Soap (4.4 oz.)
By Skin TypeSensitiveOilyNormalDry
By ProductTonerSkin Care SetsSerumsSensitive ProductsLotionsDark Spot CorrectorsCleansersBody Oils
By ProblemSun ProtectionDry SkinDark SpotsAcne
FAQsOur StoryTestimonialsBlogCustomer SupportStore Locator
Home    Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyYour Privacy is ImportantAt ClearEssence.com, we know that your privacy is important to you. It’s important to us too. That’s why we want you to know about the personal information we collect, how we use that information and with whom it may be shared. You’re Always in Control The only personal information that we collect is information that you give us when you register and when you purchase. We use that information to service your account and to personalize your experience at ClearEssence.com. We’ll never share that information with third parties interested in e-mailing you or sending promotional offers without your consent.The Information We Gather When you create an account on the Clear Essence website, we ask for basic information like your name and e-mail address. If you decide to make a purchase, we then ask you for your shipping and billing addresses, phone number and payment information. You can change any of this information at any time by logging into your account. You have the option to use certain services, such as “Tell a Friend”, which may require you to provide us with transmittal information on your friends or family. We only use this information to provide the requested service. You have the option within the site, to provide us with information on your movie preferences or other interests. We use this information to improve the level of customization in the store and provide better recommendations for you. If you enter a Clear Essence sweepstakes, we will ask for your name, address, and email address, so that we may notify winners. You do not have to be an account holder to enter a Clear Essence sweepstakes. We may also use your email address to send you special offer emails in the future. You can choose not to receive these special offer emails on the sweepstakes entry form. Don’t worry; if you choose not to receive our special offer emails, it will not affect your chances of winning. We also keep track of customer purchases, traffic patterns and related site usage inside our website to help us shape our recommendations about merchandise in the store, manage promotions and advertising, and improve our web page and site design. From time to time, we may randomly contact customers about participating in a survey about our website. These surveys are optional, and we use the responses to help us identify customer concerns and needs so that we can improve or develop new services on the website. Why Your Transactions are SecureWe use state-of-the-art encryption technology to safeguard your transactions through our payment processor, PayLeap. The technology used is SSL (Secure Socket Layer), which is supported by both the Firefox and Internet Explorer web browsers that are version 3.0 or newer. Your information, including your credit card information, is encrypted and cannot be read as it travels over the Internet. We never display your full credit card information. Your account is password-protected. You cannot submit an order or view your personal information without your password. The site will sign you out automatically if your session remains inactive for more than 2 hours. If you share a computer, we recommend that you always sign out before leaving it unattended. What You Should Know About Cookies Cookies are small pieces of information that we send through your browser to your hard drive. With “auto sign-in” turned on, a cookie lets us recognize you and provide a more meaningful and personalized shopping experience when you come back to our site. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies automatically, but you can change this setting. See your browser’s “help topics” to learn how to change the setting. If you decide not to accept cookies, you’ll still be able to shop with us and access all your account information. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of the features of Clear Essence, so we recommend that you keep them “on.” With Whom is the Information Shared? We may release specific personal information for the following reasons: We use outside companies to provide you with the merchandise you purchase, to provide some of the services you use on our site as well as for managing some of our internal operations such as databases, data analysis and e-mails. As a result, these companies do have access to the specific information necessary to provide you with your goods or services, but we require them to keep this information confidential and not to use it for any other reason. We will release your personal information to the proper persons when we believe, in good faith, that we are required to comply with a law or legal process, enforce our user agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of ClearEssence.com or other persons or entities.Aggregate Statistics From time to time we provide aggregate statistics about our members, site traffic, sales and other site-related information to reputable companies. “Aggregate” is the key word here. You can be assured that we never include information that allows these companies to identify you individually. Of course, if you have registered in an outside customer reward program in which ClearEssence.com is a participating merchant, we will provide your reward program with the necessary information about your purchases so that you can be awarded your points or other rewards. E-Mail AddressesWe never rent or sell your name and e-mail address to other on-line marketers of products or services without your consent. You make the decisions on how you would like to hear from us and if you are interested in receiving valuable offers from other reputable marketers of products and services. In addition, all promotional email that you receive from ClearEssence.com will always allow you to unsubscribe to future email promotions if you decide to do so at a later date. Postal Mailing ListsWe make our postal mailing list available to selected companies whose products and services we think you will enjoy. Once again, you have the option of removing your name and address from our mailing list by simply emailing us at ekulocs@ekulousa.com. External Sites ClearEssence.com may run sweepstakes with select companies or place advertisements or other promotional offers from select companies on our website or in our emails. When you choose to participate in these sweepstakes or promotional offers, you may link to these businesses’ websites and be asked to give them personal information or we may send over your personal information if you enter it on the ClearEssence.com website. These businesses operate independently from ClearEssence.com. Any personal information that is given to them is at your option and is no longer controlled by our privacy policy. To avoid confusion, we will identify these businesses as independent from ClearEssence.com, if the information entry point is inside of the ClearEssence.come website. We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies, if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information.Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) Clear Essence.com is a website directed to the general public. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. ConsentBy using ClearEssence.com and providing us with your personal information, you are accepting the privacy practices described in this policy statement. We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check back here occasionally. You will always find the latest version posted here. Updates to our Privacy Policy that would affect how we treat your personal information will not apply to information collected before we made the update, unless we first obtain your consent. Please note that because a customer information database is customarily considered a business asset, Clear Essence shall have the right to transfer it in a merger or sale of some or all of its company or in an action for bankruptcy. Your information will continue to be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy by the acquiring or merged company unless you are notified and provided an opportunity to opt of any changes. CommentsIf you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy please send us an e-mail at ekulocs@ekulousa.com.
SUBSCRIBE TO OUR EMAIL NEWSLETTER FOR BEAUTY TIPS AND MONEY SAVING COUPONS:
Yes! Please Sign me up to receive emails.Leave this field empty if you're human:
